sciquest.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Jaggaer

Effective: May 25, 2018  
Prior Version: July 27, 2017

* * *

This Marketing Privacy Policy and Website Terms of Use describes the information that SciQuest, Inc. d.b.a. JAGGAER and its subsidiaries, including BravoSolution and Pool4Tool, (“JAGGAER”) collects about you as a visitor to our website at [https://www.jaggaer.com](https://www.jaggaer.com/) and informs you how JAGGAER uses this information and describes your choices regarding certain types of processing.

The data controller for the information you provide or that we collect from you as a visitor to our website is:

SciQuest, Inc. d.b.a. JAGGAER  
3020 Carrington Mill Blvd., Suite 100  
Morrisville, NC 27560

This Marketing Privacy Policy does not cover any information or data collected by JAGGAER when you are using JAGGAER’s software applications and services. Please see <https://www.jaggaer.com/service-privacy-policy/>.

###  **Personal Information JAGGAER Processes**

JAGGAER collects personal information about you when you visit our website when you voluntarily provide it. For example, on certain pages you may choose to provide JAGGAER with your name, e-mail address, telephone number or other information to request details about JAGGAER, including information about JAGGAER’s software applications and services. This information enables JAGGAER to follow up with you after your visit.

###  **Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

JAGGAER does not sell personal information collected through its website.

JAGGAER will not share any personal information with third parties unless: (i) authorized by you in writing, (ii) the third parties are service providers authorized by JAGGAER to perform services for the purposes set forth in this Marketing Privacy Policy, and only when agreements are in place that require each third party to protect the privacy and confidentiality of the personal information that is shared and comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws, (iii) the third parties are partners  with whom JAGGAER collaborates to make additional services available to you and only when agreements are in place that require each third party to protect the privacy and confidentiality of the personal information that is shared and comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws; (iv) reasonably necessary to comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant, government investigation or other legal requirements, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or (v) necessary for the prevention or detection of crime (subject in each case to applicable law) or  to establish or defend a legal claim.

###  **Use of JAGGAER’s Websites**

JAGGAER, or JAGGAER-authorized service providers, may observe your activities, preferences and data relating to your use of our websites. JAGGAER uses this collected or logged information to diagnose website technical problems. JAGGAER or our authorized service provider also use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our websites.

###  **Cookies**

JAGGAER uses technology that many other websites employ, including “cookies,” to collect information.

Cookies are small text files that are sent to or accessed from your web browser or your computer’s hard drive.  A cookie typically contains the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie originated, the “lifetime” of the cookie (i.e., when it expires) and a randomly generated unique number or similar identifier. A cookie also may contain information about your computer, such as user settings, browsing history and activities conducted while using our website. JAGGAER does not use cookies to read any other information on your computer’s hard drive.

We use first-party cookies and third-party cookies. First-party cookies are placed on your device directly by us. For example, we use first-party cookies to adapt our website to your browser’s language preferences and to better understand your use of our website. Third-party cookies are placed on your device by our partners and service providers. For example, we use third-party cookies to measure user numbers on our website.

Session cookies only last until you close your browser. We use session cookies for a variety of reasons, including to learn more about your use of our website during one single browser session and to help you to use our website more efficiently. Persistent cookies have a longer lifespan and aren’t automatically deleted when you close your browser. These types of cookies are primarily used for analytical purposes.

JAGGAER also uses web beacons, or transparent GIF files, provided by our service provider to report activity on our site. The beacons help us manage our online advertising and measure its effectiveness. These files enable our service provider to recognize a cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements are most effective.

You can set your browser to refuse cookies or to warn you before a cookie is placed. In those jurisdictions where active consent is required, JAGGAER employs “pop-ups” to obtain such consent. Please note that changes you make to your cookie preferences may make browsing our website a less satisfying experience. In some cases, you may even find yourself unable to use all or part of our website.

To learn more about cookies and other data collection technology, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

###  **Retargeted Advertising**

Retargeted advertising uses information collected on an individual’s web browsing behavior such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is used to display more relevant information to you on the JAGGAER website. This information is also used to display JAGGAER employment opportunities to you if you have visited our careers page. The information collected is only linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for retargeted advertising either comes from JAGGAER or through third party website publishers.

###  **What about Do Not Track Signals?**

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome) have a “Do Not Track” (“ **DNT** ”) feature that tells a website that a user does not want to have his or her online activity tracked.  If a website that responds to a DNT signal receives a DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser’s user.  Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform.  For this reason, many businesses, including JAGGAER, do not respond to DNT signals.

###  **Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button, and widgets, such as the “Share this” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These features may collect your IP address, record which page you are visiting on our sites and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###  **Opt-out; Access**

If at any time after registering for information, you change your mind about receiving information from us, please click on the “opt-out” link in the communication or send us a request at [privacy@jaggaer.com](mailto:privacy@jaggaer.com) specifying your new choice. Please note this does not opt you out of receiving generic ads.

If you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate or if you believe that we are no longer entitled to use it and want to request its rectification, deletion or object to its processing, please contact us [privacy@jaggaer.com](mailto:privacy@jaggaer.com). JAGGAER will respond to the request within thirty (30) business days.

JAGGAER will provide you with the information you have sought by email or, if possible, in another form that you have requested.   To protect your privacy, we may ask you to verify your identity or provide additional information before we let you access or update your information. We may reject requests for certain reasons, including if the request is unlawful or if it may infringe on trade secrets, intellectual property or privacy of another user. If JAGGAER decides to deny you access to some or all of your personal information, JAGGAER will notify you in writing of our decision within thirty (30) business days and explain why and how you can complain if you are not satisfied with our decision.

###  ** ** **Children’s privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 because they are not allowed to use our website.  If you know that a user is under the age of 18, please contact us at [privacy@jaggaer.com](mailto:privacy@jaggaer.com).

###  **Resident of California?**

If you are a California resident, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information about you that we have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To request this notice, please submit your request at <https://www.jaggaer.com/trustcenter/privacy/inquiry/>. Please allow 30 days for a response.  At this time, JAGGAER does not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

###  **JAGGAER EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework Privacy Statement**

If you are located in the European Union or Switzerland, this section of this Marketing Privacy Policy provides notice that your personal information may be processed in the United States. JAGGAER complies with the applicable provisions of the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information transferred to the United States from the European Union and Switzerland, respectively. JAGGAER has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms of this Marketing Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view JAGGAER’s certification, please visit: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

###  **Complaint Handling; Dispute Resolution**

In compliance with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, JAGGAER commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Marketing Privacy Policy should contact JAGGAER at: [privacy@jaggaer.com](mailto:privacy@jaggaer.com).

JAGGAER has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. Additionally, in accordance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield, an individual may, under certain conditions, invoke binding arbitration.

###  **Investigations; Enforcement; Liability**

As a result of JAGGAER’s adherence to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, JAGGAER is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, JAGGAER is potentially liable.

###  **Contact Details**

At any time you may contact JAGGAER with questions or concerns about this Marketing Privacy Policy at [privacy@jaggaer.com](mailto:privacy@jaggaer.com). You also may communicate with us at:

SciQuest, Inc. dba JAGGAER  
Attention: General Counsel  
3020 Carrington Mill Blvd. Suite 100  
Morrisville, NC 27560

If you are located in the European Union and have any questions about this Marketing Privacy Policy, you also may contact the Supervisory Authority of your country of residence (see <http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>).

###  **Data Retention**

We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes or, if linger, as required or permitted by applicable law.

###  **Security**

JAGGAER maintains a comprehensive, written information security program that contains industry standard administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect your information against unauthorized access, theft and loss.

JAGGAER limits access to personal information to those persons and authorized service providers who have a specific business purpose for maintaining and processing such information. JAGGAER’s employees who have been granted physical access to personal information are made aware of their responsibilities to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of that information and have been provided training and instruction on how to do so.

###  **Changes to our Marketing Privacy Policy**

This Marketing Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth at the top of this page. JAGGAER reserves the right to modify this Marketing Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes to technology, legal obligations and information handling practices.

JAGGAER will alert you to any changes by indicating at the top of this page the date this Marketing Privacy Policy is effective and when it was last revised. We will notify you in writing before any material change takes effect so that you have time to review the change and decide whether you would like to continue to use our website under the terms of the revised Marketing Privacy Policy.
